On Sunday May 15th, 2016, Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophetic message about the nation of Venezuela.
These were his words:
Hallelujah.
I will continue to pray on my own for your country and for the world.
But there is one now that is very, very close
which I will just say briefly -
Venezuela - it's a Spanish nation.
This Venezuelan country - I'm seeing...
which I'm praying that God should avert it -
I'm seeing a coup that will take them back to their...
I mean, that will throw away the democratic system of government.
Pray for this country because it is very close - that is why I'm saying this.
Anytime you pray, remember a nation like that.
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 29/01/2019